骑士！骑士！
Horsemen! Horsemen!
骑士！骑士！骑士！骑士！
Horsemen! Horsemen! Horsemen! Horsemen!
你该不会真以为……我们把你丢下了吧？
Did you think we abandoned you?
还是说，你觉得我们的魔术已经玩不出新花样了？
Or that we'd run out of magic?
那么，女士们先生们，再想想吧，
Well, think again, ladies and gentlemen,
因为好戏 这才刚要开场
because you are about to be amazed.
既然此刻你人在这儿，就说明你
If you're here right now, then you have
破解了谜题，跟上了线索
followed the clues and cracked the code.
恭喜你，欢迎入局
Congratulations, and welcome.
距离骑士上次现身，已经过去了十年，
It's been 10 years since the horseman last appeared,
但我们回来了！
but we are back!
好了，来，靠近点   嗯，再近一点
Okay, so, come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你以为看到的越多，
Because the more you think you see,
就越容易将老把戏重新包装
the easier it will be to dress up old tricks
并骗你以为是新的
and fool you that they are new.
那么，我叫 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯，
So, my name is J. Daniel Atlas,
请允许我像往常一样发言，
and allow me to speak as I often do
为我那些不那么有魅力的同事们，我想说...
for my less charismatic colleagues when I say...
呼！回来真好！
Whoo! It is very good to be back!
没错   没错   我们是消失了一阵子，
Yes. Yes. We vanished for a while,
但在魔法的世界里，
but in the world of magic,
所有消失的，终将重现
everything that disappears, reappears.
不过，至少戏法要是变得够漂亮才行
Well, at least if the trick is done right.
我是梅里特·麦金尼
I'm Merritt McKinney.
不像我这位，呃，铁哥们儿丹尼，
Unlike my, uh, very good buddy here, Danny,
今晚在座的各位，大多都把那份自大留在门外了
most of you checked your egos at the door tonight.
你们竟然找到了这个小众的地下集会
You found this little underground soiree
因为你们就是想被耍一回
because you wanted to get fooled.
嘿，大家好   我是杰克·怀尔德
Hey, everyone. I'm Jack Wilder.
战争、疫情、气候变化、人工智能
Wars, pandemics, climate change, AI.
说实话，我们比以往任何时候都更需要魔法
Let's face it, we all need magic more than ever.
所以我要你们非常仔细地观察
So I want you to pay very close attention.
接下来的这场好戏，你们可千万别眨眼
You are not gonna want to miss this next trick.
亨莉·里夫斯，现在是亨莉·里夫斯·斯坦利了
Henley Reeves, now Henley Reeves Stanley.
三个孩子，两只狗，还有一个硕士学位
Three kids, two dogs and a master's degree.
好久不见
It's been a while.
想我们了吗？
Did you miss us?
那些家伙当年可真了不起
Those guys were great back in the day.
我曾经想成为一名魔术师
I used to want to be a magician.
然后我到了12岁
And then I turned 12.
当心点，隔墙有耳
Careful, they might be listening.
哦，我吓得连我身上这件AllSaints外套都在抖呢
Ooh, I'm shaking in my AllSaints.
他们能怎么样？
What are they gonna do?
那是真金吗？
Is that real gold?
什么？ 那是真金吗？
What? Is that real gold?
是啊，我很有钱
Yeah, I'm rich.
伙计，这是魔术表演
This is a magic show, dude.
这里的每个傻瓜都是扒手，
Every fool here is a pickpocket,
或是扒手手里的傻瓜
or a pickpocket's fool.
刚才那是俳句吗？什么意思？
Was that a haiku? What was that?
你们每个人都刚刚收到一张扑克牌
Each of you just received a playing card.
如果你们不介意，呃，把它拿出来好吗？
If you wouldn't mind, uh, pulling it out?
好   现在，我们要洗牌了，
Right. Now, we're gonna shuffle the deck,
所以每个人找到身边的一个随机的人
so everybody find a random person near them
和他们交换牌
and switch cards with them.
等你们交换完之后，
And then when you've done that,
再找另一个人和他交换
find somebody else and switch with them.
好了，很好   呃，现在...
Okay, great. Uh, now...
呃，哒哒哒哒哒... 那边的那位，下面的那位
Uh, duhduhduhduhduh... You there, down there.
我吗？ 对   你的牌是什么？
Me? Yeah. What is your card?
方块A    方块A   好的
Ace of diamonds. Ace of diamonds. Okay.
我们让事情变得更有趣一点
Let's make things a little more complicated here.
这里有谁还有方块A吗？
Does anybody else here have the ace of diamonds?
等等，是我   方块A！
Wait, it's me. Ace of diamonds!
哦！
Ooh!
看来我们有了一个第五骑士，名字不是卢拉
Looks like we have a Fifth Horseman not named Lula.
上台来，你来当我们的助手
Come up on stage, you're gonna be our helper.
动手吧！ 手下2：没错，快动手！
Do it! MAN 2: Yeah, go!
现在，呃，看着我的眼睛
Now, uh, look into my eyes
然后... 睡吧
and... sleep.
宝刀未老
Still got it.
现在，这孩子在你们看来可能很普通，
Now, this might look like an ordinary kid to you,
但今晚，他将像被附身一样表演非凡的魔术
but tonight, he is going to do extraordinary magic
如同被附身的人
like a man possessed.
字面意思
Literally.
亨莉    什么事，梅里特
Henley. Yes, Merritt.
你介意进入他的身体吗？
Would you mind stepping inside his body?
是的   还有，杰克，呃，
Yep. And, Jack, uh,
你为什么不也跳进来呢？
why don't you throw yourself on in there, too?
我最擅长这个了
What I do best.
还有... 哦，上帝保佑你
And... Oh, God help you.
阿特拉斯，你不也滑进来吗？
Atlas, why don't you slither on inside, as well?
我也不妨挤进去
And I might as well wedge myself in there, too.
创造魔法需要一个村庄
It takes a village to make magic.
哦！哇！
Oh! Whoa!
J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯在此
J. Daniel Atlas in the house.
那么，谁想看魔术？
So, who wants to see a magic trick?
交给你了，梅里特
Take it away, Merritt.
哈喽，你们这些美丽的家伙
Hello, you beautiful people.
大家都知道梅里特·麦金尼会读心术
Now, everyone knows that Merritt McKinney reads minds.
那么现在，我就是他   或者说他是我   谁知道呢？
Well, now, I'm him. Or he's me. Who knows?
呃，我感觉到今晚有人来这里
Uh, I'm sensing someone came here tonight
不是为了享受魔术，而是来搞破坏
not to enjoy magic, but to tear it down.
现场有布雷特·芬尼根吗？
Is there a Brett Finnegan in the house?
什么事？
What up?
现在，你和你的朋友们在这里
Now, you and your friends here
建立了坎普霍巴特加密货币交易所
set up the Camp Hobart Crypto Exchange.
事实   是的   没错    我们就是干这个的
Fact. Yep. Yeah. It's what we're about.
拿走了纽约市的
Took the good people of New York's
雇员退休金和福利基金一半的现金
employee pension and welfare fund half its cash.
呃，你夸大其词了，
Uh, you're rounding up,
而且，风险都明确说明过了
and also, the risks were laid out very clearly.
大家都知道自己要面对什么，伙计
Everybody knew what they were getting into, dude.
你把利润藏在海外了吗？
Did you hide the profits offshore?
账户尾号是
Account ending
53297？
in 53297?
没有我的，呃... 你不可能知道那个
You couldn't know that without my, uh...
哦，这是真金吗？
Oh, is this real gold?
布雷特，你应该更小心
Brett, you ought to be more careful
保管你的东西，伙计
with your things, man.
梅里特是通灵者，但我，杰克，
Merritt's a psychic, but me, Jack,
我擅长手法魔术
I'm into sleight of hand.
问问你的朋友们
Ask your friends.
他们刚刚为缩小贫富差距出了一份力
They've just done their part to close the wealth gap.
什么？搞什么...
What? What the...
现在，来点小再分配
Now, here's a little redistribution.
嘿！嘿，嘿！
Hey! Hey, hey!
谢谢   谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你等着吃官司吧，伙计！我会揍扁你！
Lawyer up, dude! I'll kick your ass!
哦哦！
Uhoh!
有人忘了亨莉会飞
Someone forgot Henley can fly.
剩下的交给我们吧，但请大家鼓掌
We can take it from here, but a round of applause
献给台上最棒的骑士
for the best Horseman on stage.
呼！哇
Whoo! Wow.
嘿，嘿，嘿   嘿，嘿
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey.
太棒了   那么，大家，拿起你们的饮料，
Fantastic. So, everybody, I want you to take your drink,
把它倒在你们的牌面上
and I want you to pour it onto the face of your card.
能做到吗？
Can you do that?
你们每张牌上的那12个独特的词
Those 12 unique words on each of your cards
是你们新加密货币钱包的密码
form the password to your new crypto wallet.
哦！ 登录
Oh! Log on
你就会发现布雷特偷走的数百万...
and you'll find Brett's stolen millions more...
得到了更公平的重新分配
fairly redistributed.
我的天哪   五... 5万美金！
Oh, my God. Fifty... 50,000 bucks!
5万！
50,000!
你完蛋了，伙计！
You're freaking done, dude!
哇，哇！冷静点，姜饼人，
Whoa, whoa! Cool your head, gingerbread,
因为我有个预感
'cause I am having a vision.
呃，也许警察马上就要破门而入了！
Eh, maybe cops are gonna come bursting through that door!
所以你自己也表演个魔术吧
So perform a magic trick of your own
在三，二，一的倒计时后消失
and disappear in three, two, one.
现在靠近点   嗯，再近一点
Now come in close. Mm, closer.
因为你以为看到的越多，就越容易
Because the more you think you see, the easier it will be
将老把戏重新包装... 什么？
to dress up old tricks... What?
并骗你以为是新的
and fool you that they are new.
哦，我的天哪，不
Oh, my God, no.
不！
No!
《惊天魔盗团3》
听着，在我看来，我觉得你做得很好
Look, in my opinion, I think you did a great job.
呃，我觉得我演阿特拉斯演得不错
Uh, I think my Atlas was good.
我演的梅里特可能还需要改进
My Merritt could probably use some work.
嗯    就像圣地亚哥的瘾君子
Mm. It's like a San Diego stoner
和捕虾船船长生的孩子
and a shrimp boat captain had a baby.
当然
Sure.
不，说真的，博斯科，我不知道你是怎么做到的
No, seriously, Bosco, I don't know how you do it.
好的模仿不仅仅是模仿
A good impersonation isn't just about the mimicry.
它关乎对细节的关注，
It's about attention to detail,
个性和细微差别
personality and nuance.
好吧   好吧   让我试试，让我试试
Okay. Okay. Let me try, let me try.
嗯... 我是 J·丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Um... I'm J. Daniel Atlas.
你看得越仔细，看到的就越少
The closer you look, the less you see.
还差点意思
It was something.
是的   呃，你多练练
Yep. Uh, you'll work on it.
我演得还行啊    是个好的开始
I wasn't bad. It was a good start.
但还需要改进    好吧，当然
But it could use some work. Okay, sure.
你一直在看什么？ 没什么，没什么，没什么
What do you keep looking at? Nothing, nothing, nothing.
伙计，高兴点   伙计们，打起精神来！看看我们！
Dude, cheer up. Guys, come on! Look at us!
看看我们走了多远   我们今晚大获全胜
Look at how far we've come. We totally scored tonight.
好吧，下次你戴粉红色的假发，好吗？
All right, next time, you wear the pink wig, okay?
不要
No.
伙计，又锁上了    好吧，我来开锁
Dude, it's locked again. Okay, I'll pick it.
等等，等等，等一下   表演一下那个
Wait, wait, wait, hold on. Do the thing.
不要    求你了，表演一下那个
No. Please do the thing.
完全没必要    太酷了
It's so unnecessary. It's so cool.
我来帮你拿包    完全没必要
I'll hold your bag. It's so unnecessary.
来吧，很有趣的    好吧
Come on, it's fun. Okay.
你可以的
You got this.
她像个小马里奥    她确实像马里奥
She's like a little Mario. She is like Mario.
小心，小心   千万别死
Careful, careful. Please don't die.
你还好吗？ 琼：没事
Are you okay? JUNE: Yeah.